

# Vlad Leontescu

Bucharest, Romania lvlad27@gmail.com +40 0758 076 445

https://www.linkedin.com/in/vladleontescu/

https://lvlad27.github.io/Portfolio/

After working for several years as a structural engineer, I developed a strong desire to learn and grow in the tech industry, with a growing passion for software development and would like to take any opportunity that can help me pursue this. Currently I am studying Web Development, but I also have a strong interest for Cybersecurity. I'm a fast learner with a strong technical and engineering background, self-learning enthusiast, used to organise and follow deadlines and working under time constraints.

### **Educational Background**

# Technical University of Civil Engineering

Bucharest

Master of Engineering - MEng 2013 - 2015

# Technical University of Civil Engineering

Bucharest

Bachelor of Engineering - BE 2009- 2013

# **Tudor Vianu National College** of Computer Science

Bucharest 2005 - 2009

#### **Skills & Proficiencies**

- Responsive Web Design
- Front End Development
- HTML5 | SCSS
- JavaScript ES6
- npm
- Git | GitHub
- VS Code
- WordPress
- Linux
- Structural Design & Detailing
- Structural Analysis
- BIM modelling

## **Work Experience**

#### **Structural Engineer**

**WSP** Romania

November 2016 - September 2021

CAD Engineering, 3d Modelling, Structural Detailing using Tekla Structures, Robot Structural Analysis. Collaboration with remote teams from Sweden. Establish, organize and follow through with project deadlines.

#### **Structural Engineer**

K-BOX

May 2016 - October 2016

Structural Design, 3d Modelling, Structural Detailing using Etabs, Tekla Structures, Advance Steel, Microsoft Office.

#### **Structural Engineer**

**DCTS** 

*April 2015 - March 2016* 

Structural Design, 3d Modelling, Structural Detailing using Etabs, Tekla Structures, AutoCad, Microsoft Office.

#### Certifications

#### freeCodeCamp

Responsive Web Design

JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures

2022

Attended online certification courses. https://www.freecodecamp.org/lvlad

#### Languages

English \*\*\*\*

Spanish \*

French ★